{"data":[{"question":"Many people go to church _____ Sunday morning.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for seasons, months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for specific day and dates (on Sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"2"},{"question":"Mrs. Smith was notified_____ a Wednesday afternoon last March.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for seasons, months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for specific day and dates (on Sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"2"},{"question":"Conditions in France were deplorable _____ 1793.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for seasons, months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for specific day and dates (on Sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"2"},{"question":"Are you going away ____ Easter.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"- At: used  with holiday periods, meaning the few days around the holiday","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"2"},{"question":"We saw a ballet _____ Julia's birthday.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for seasons, months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for specific day and dates (on Sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"2"},{"question":"We're moving house ____ two months.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for seasons, months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for specific day and dates (on Sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"2"},{"question":"We're moving house ____ two months.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for seasons, months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for specific day and dates (on Sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"2"},{"question":"Are you going away on holiday _____ summer?","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for seasons, months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for specific day and dates (on Sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"2"},{"question":"We're flying to Beijing ____ 2 June.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for seasons, months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for specific day and dates (on Sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"2"},{"question":"David bought his car _____ 1998.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for seasons, months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for specific day and dates (on Sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"2"}]}